To protect and surf.
Meet the Deedles is a comedy, family film directed by Steve Boyum.
Two surfers end up as Yellowstone park rangers and have to
stop a former ranger who is out for revenge.
Phil Deedle, played by Paul Walker.
Capt. Douglas Pine, played by John Ashton.
Frank Slater, played by Dennis Hopper.
Elton Deedle, played by Eric Braeden.
Crabbe, played by Richard Lineback.
Nemo, played by Robert Englund.
Meet the Deedles is a 1998 American comedy film directed by Steve Boyum in his directorial debut, and starring Paul Walker and Steve Van Wormer as two twin surfers, Stew and Phil Deedle,
reprimanded by their father, mistakenly land at Yellowstone Park as recruiters but bigger problems await them including fighting Frank Slater (Dennis Hopper), an ex-ranger.
This was the first live-action film from DIC Entertainment.
Released theatrically by Buena Vista Pictures in the United States on
March 27, 1998, the film was universally panned by critics.
It was also a box-office bomb, grossing only $4.4
million against a $24 million budget.
The film explores themes of surfer, wyoming, usa,
national park, twins, park ranger.
The tone is lighthearted.